dragonpay.ph 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of Dragonpay Corporation. This privacy policy applies to information collected by this website, the Dragonpay mobile credits app and all our payment selection pages which are integrated to our merchant partners’ websites. This does not include, however, the information provided when a user leaves our site. By visiting www.dragonpay.ph and continuing to use Dragonpay’s main and extended services, you signify that you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Policy.

**Information Collection**

Dragonpay Corporation is the sole owner of the information collected on this site automatically as you use our website and other services. We also collect information from third parties such as other Dragonpay users, clients or customers for the purpose of providing our services to you. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you through our main and extended services which include payment selection pages, mobile applications, management systems and other services.

**Information Use and Sharing**

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not sell or rent the information we gather from you to anyone. We will not share your information with any third party outside our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request and efficiently provide our services to you, e.g. to check payment validation. We may also use your information for marketing and other purposes unless you opted out (where available) by unsubscribing from marketing emails and/or by contacting us. We may use your information, such as your email address and phone number to send you special offers and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about services or information that we think may interest you.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Whenever we collect sensitive information (such as bank information or payment details) that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (ex. Customer support or billing) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If Dragonpay is required by law to process the information for any legal purpose, Dragonpay will provide you with prior notice of this requirement, unless Dragonpay is prohibited by law from providing such notice.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Dragonpay Corporation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Use of Cookies**

We and our third-party service providers use cookies and other tracking mechanisms (like google analytics) to track information about your use of our Website and Services. We may combine this information with other personal information that we collect from you. These cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Website and Services. Upon continuing to use our services and sites, you signify your acceptance and consent to allow us to use such cookies needed for the efficient use of our services.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Dragonpay may amend this policy from time to time and updates will be posted on this page. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email admin@dragonpay.ph

**Disclaimer**

Dragonpay reserves the right to amend its policies, and any content on its website without prior notice.
